♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Okay, okay, I got one.
Would you rather have dinner and
then sex with Megan Fox's body
with Leonard Nimoy's
head on it
or reroof an entire
condo complex by yourself?
Oh, boy.
Can I close my eyes?
No, eye contact the whole time
and a lot of kissing.
Well, how about Megan Fox's head
on Leonard Nimoy's body?
I know, somehow
that's better.
The hybrid organism exists
as I've described it.
How many units
are in the condo?
Thirty-two.
Tile roof or shingles?
Yeah, 'cause it
makes a difference
what you're carrying
up that ladder.
Wait, whose neck is it?
Huh?
I mean, where's the cutoff?
You know,
is it Megan Fox's neck
or am I burying my face in
Leonard Nimoy's turkey gizzard?
Nimoy's neck.
You have got yourself a roof.
I'll take the
Spock-Fox intercourse.
All right, Peter,
your turn.
Uh... boxers or briefs?
What?
That's the worst one
I've ever heard.
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm exhausted, all right?
I-I didn't get any sleep
'cause Brian
and the neighbor's dog
kept me up all night.
BRIAN:
Hello?
DOG: Hello.
Are you a dog?
Yes!
I am also a dog.
All right!
Yeah!
We're dogs!
Yeah, we're dogs!
We're dogs that live
near each other!
DOG 2: Hey, are
you guys dogs?
Yeah!
We're totally dogs!
Yeah, both of us!
Oh, wow. Well, if you're
that tired, Peter,
maybe you should
have some coffee.
Yeah, or you could
have some Red Bull.
Red Bull?
What the hell is Red Bull?
You never heard of Red Bull?
It's an energy drink.
Here you go, Peter.
It's on the house.
So? What do you think?
♪ And I feel
like I just got home ♪
♪ And I feel ♪
♪ And I feel
like I just got home ♪
♪ And I feel... ♪
Good evening.
Our top story tonight:
Barack Obama makes a visit
to James Woods High School.
Yes, it's time to get
jiggy with it, Quahog--
I thought
we had taken that out.
President Barack Obama
will visit James Woods High
next month, and this little town
of ours couldn't be more abuzz.
Oh, my God, this is
gonna be so amazing!
It's all anybody in my class
is talking about.
Darn it, why is
this so hard?!
What's wrong, Chris?
Just 'cause Obama's coming,
everybody in my English class
has to write a stupid
essay about hope.
But this is all I
can come up with.
Chris, this is just a shaded-in
triangle and the word "muff."
For God's sakes, Meg,
it's a first draft.
Just tell me if you
think the tone is right.
Well, I don't know
what this is,
but it's not what hope
is about, Chris.
Well, if you're such a genius,
you tell me what hope is.
Hope is what gets you
out of bed in the morning
when it's the day of prom
and you haven't been asked.
Hope pushes the caterpillar
through the cocoon
and drives the salmon upstream.
Your breasts may be small
and your glasses may be thick,
but hope doesn't
hold up a mirror.
Hope is a horizon we head for,
leaving nothing behind us
but fear.
And though we may
never reach our goals,
it's hope that will save us
from who we once were.
Wow.
Did you learn
that at school?
No. You can't just learn
creative writing, Chris.
It's got to be inside you,
like musical talent
or athleticism or the ability
to choose to be gay.
I don't think
they choose that.
Oh, please,
(doorknob rattling)
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey!
What's up, party people?
Ah, what the hell
are these things,
curtains or something? Boring!
- Holy smoke, it's crowded in here.
- Hey!
There, ah, that's terrific;
it opens up the whole room.
Peter, there
you are.
Where the hell
have you been?
I've been
worried sick.
Oh, so I had a few Red Bulls,
drove to New York.
What's the big deal?
Ah, there's my little man!
(shuddering)
Done!
Wow, Dad, that
was pretty cool.
Can I try
some Red Bull?
Oh, my God, can you
try some Red Bull?
Chris, I'd take it
as an insult if you didn't.
Here you go, have some cans,
one, two, three, four, five.
Go on, take 'em, take 'em,
take 'em, take 'em, take 'em.
(laughs) That's what
Woody Woodpecker says.
All right, I'm gonna go outside
and milk the cow.
Peter, where'd
you get that cow?
Oh, that's a silly
question, Lois.
I bought it so we can have
fresh milk every day.
(mooing)
Whoa, boy, that Red Bull's
some strong stuff.
(screaming)
Hey, everybody, welcome back
to The Price Is Right.
Time to spin the wheel.
Top winner
for the day is Peter,
so you're gonna be
the first to spin it.
Go ahead, Peter,
close as you can
to a dollar
without going over.
(beeping)
All right, while we're waiting
for the wheel to spin,
you want to say hi to anybody?
Oh, yeah, Drew, I
want to say hi to
Lois, Brian, Chris, Stewie,
Meg, Joe, Bonnie, Quagmire,
Cleveland, Mort, Seamus, Adam
West, Dr. Hartman, Bruce,
Carter, Babs, Tom Tucker,
Angela, Opie, Carl, Herbert,
Jillian, Consuela, Giant
Chicken, Greased-up Deaf Guy!
(chuckles):
Okay.
I'm sure they're
happy to hear that.
(crowd screaming)
Whoa, paramedics,
come on down!
(laughing frantically)
Mom, oh, my God,
guess what!
Oh, God! You scared
the (bleep) out of me.
You know that essay about hope
I had to write?
Well, the principal said it was
the best one in the class,
and he wants me to read it aloud
to introduce the President!
Ah, Chris,
that's incredible!
Remember when I used to
come to school to wipe you,
and I'd say, "Someday I won't
have to wipe you anymore
and you'll do great things"?
Well, this has been
a big year for us.
Wait a second.
Give me that.
"Hope pushes the caterpillar
through the cocoon
and drives the salmon upstream."
I wrote that!
You stole
this from me.
Hey, you didn't say
I couldn't use it.
But now you get to meet the
President of the United States
because of
what I wrote.
Ugh! I bet you don't even
know what his first name is.
I-I don't know-- Mike?
Hey, what are
you doing?
Lois, where is my Red Bull?
Peter, I got
rid of it.
Why the hell
would you do that?!
It was making you crazy,
and it's not good for you.
That's why I poured it
all out in the garden.
(grunting)
(tires screech)
Official flower business.
(tires screeching)
What are you doing, Peter?
I'm making my
own Red Bull.
Lois can't stop me
from experiencing
the manic highs and
lows my body demands.
Whoa, whoa, hang on,
you're adding kerosene?
Peter, that's insane.
That'll destroy your body.
Kerosene is
fuel, Brian.
Red Bull is fuel.
Kerosene is
Red Bull.
Now, why don't you
leave me alone
while I'm doing
my important work?
(blender whirring)
Peter, that drink will kill you.
Brian, whatever kills
me makes me stronger.
(sighs)
See, Brian?
I feel great.
Peter?
Peter, are you alive?
(groaning)
Ah, you're alive.
Okay, I won't, uh,
I won't, uh, eat you then.
I was gonna eat you.
Dr. Hartman,
please tell me, is my
husband gonna be all right?
Uh, Cancun, actually,
thanks for asking.
Just got back.
Mrs. Griffin, I'm afraid
all the toxic chemicals
your husband ingested from
his homemade energy drink
have caused
total kidney failure.
(all gasping)
How was Cancun?
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
Kidney failure?
Is he gonna be okay?
Well, yes and no.
We'll put him on
a kidney transplant list,
but that could take months.
Until a donor is found,
he's gonna have to undergo
dialysis treatments
three times a week.
Dialysis?
Is there any other way?
Yes, there is.
No, no, no, no, no!
W-We'll do
the dialysis.
Hey, Doc, I'm here
for my dialysis.
Ah, have a seat, Peter.
Let's get you hooked up.
Doc, I don't know how much
more of this I can take.
It's been
three weeks.
I know, I saw the caption.
Yeah, but I-I just go crazy
just sitting here for so long.
Aw, I know it's tough,
but maybe there's something
I can do to make it easier.
Here, play with this
bucket of afterbirth.
Ha!
The Lockhorns.
Always locking horns.
(gasps) Oh, my God,
that's why they call it that.
Oh, Peter, you got here
just in time!
Chris is almost on.
Shh. Mom, here it is.
As Quahog prepares
for the arrival of
President Barack Obama,
it will be a very big day
for one local teenager
who will be reading his essay
to introduce the President.
I sat down with accomplished
wordsmith Chris Griffin.
"Hope is a horizon
we head for,
leaving nothing
behind us but fear."
Chris, tell me
how those words came to you.
Do you believe
in angels, Tom?
Of course I do.
Well, there you go.
I suspected angels.
It was angels.
Very good.
Chris Griffin,
a weaver of dreams
at the loom of the mind.
A weaver of dreams at
the loom of the mind.
A neat thing I just said.
And now sports.
Oh, Chris, we are
so proud of you.
I got to admit, Chris,
this is pretty exciting.
When did you become so coherent?
Mom, I wrote that!
He stole it, and he's
taking all the credit!
Chris, is that true?
You didn't write anything!
This is my essay!
Meg, is that true?
No, he's lying!
That should be me getting
to meet the President!
Meg, for God's sake, relax.
You're not the first person
to be outshined by a sibling.
What about the third
Bronte sister?
Oh, Emily, Wuthering Heights
was truly splendid.
Oh, no, Charlotte, Jane Eyre
was so very brilliant.
I made blood out
me lady parts!
Good for you.
So we've all
done something.
It's happening now.
Ah, it's a
period joke.
It's a period period joke.
Ha, ha.
Okay, moving on.
ANNOUNCER (over TV): Coming up
next, Charles in Charge.
Oh, my God!
Aw, I want to watch this, but
I got stupid dialysis at 3:00.
I am so sick of this crap
mucking up my life.
Well, Peter, I mean, what,
y-you can get away with
skipping one treatment, right?
I mean, that's not
gonna kill you.
Yeah, it's probably just
like missing an antibiotic.
You just take
the next one.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Besides,
it's Charles in Charge.
JOE:
You know what I like?
The "Charles"
part is formal,
but the "In Charge"
part is kind of casual.
QUAGMIRE:
Oh, wow. Remember this?
Remember when nobody had
any muscle tone?
Geez, how many "A's"
does that guy need?
Uh, two, apparently.
You know, it's kinda
weird that '80s white clothes
could pass for
'90s black clothes.
Yeah, is that like
a rummage sale thing?
Ah, Nicole Eggert.
Didn't she bang
somebody gross?
I don't know.
Yeah, I feel like she
banged somebody gross.
You know, I heard
the sweater budget
on this show
was 200 grand.
Didn't you tell me
that, Peter?
Oh, my God!
Peter, you don't
look so good.
What are you talkin' about?
I feel great.
Like I could go
another 20 years or more.
Dr. Hartman, this was
just too close a call.
Next time, we could be too late.
Suppose he's stuck somewhere,
or-or he's trapped in
an elevator
or God knows what else?!
He could die!
He needs a new kidney now!
Well, as I said, Mrs.
Griffin, he's on a list,
but there are a lot
of people ahead of him.
Well, what are the chances of
getting him moved up the list?
Honestly, not great.
It could be months
before he can get
a transplant.
Unless you know someone
who's a compatible organ match
and would be willing
to donate one of theirs.
I'll do it.
He could have one of my kidneys.
Well, we always check spouse
records for compatibility.
I'm afraid you're not a match.
But it turns out you are a match
for a little girl
who's dying in that next room
over there.
Oh, well, how 'bout we
concentrate
on this family, Doctor?
Well, the only other
option is your children.
No, I won't put the kids
through that.
Well, then I don't know
what else to do.
You'll just have
to roll the dice
and hope a kidney
comes through soon.
Well... what about me?
Is that possible, Doctor?
Well... I suppose.
Stranger things have
happened in medicine.
I once tried
to clone a chicken.
The result wound up
being a man-sized chicken
that was incredibly hostile and
ended up escaping from the lab.
Okay, Doc, we gotta have
a talk at some point,
but Brian, are, are, you,
are you sure about this?
Well, there's no harm in
seeing if I'm compatible.
Well, according to these
results, Brian is a match.
(all cheering)
Hooray, yay, yeah,
ice cream sounds great.
The only thing is...
Mrs. Griffin, could I speak with
you and Brian alone, please?
Well, of course.
Kids, why don't you wait in the car?
Okay, Mom.
Let's go find the big,
black sassy nurse.
There's always one.
NURSE: You can cry about it,
or you can decide to live.
It's your choice.
STEWIE:
Found her.
Hey, w-w-what is it, Doc?
Well, as a dog,
Brian's kidneys are smaller
and don't have the capacity
of a human kidney.
For the procedure
to work,
we would need
to transplant two.
But, but I only have two.
That's right.
The procedure would kill you.
Ha-ha, that car's
gettin' towed!
My God, Dr. Hartman,
isn't there any other way?
I'm afraid not,
Mrs. Griffin.
BRIAN:
I'll do it.
What?
I'll... I'll do it.
I'll give you my kidneys.
But Brian...
you'll die!
Peter, you're my best friend.
You, you gave me a home
when I didn't have one.
And you've treated me like
a family member ever since.
I wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for you.
I'd probably be dead anyway,
lying under
some freeway overpass.
And I-I-I wanna,
I wanna return the favor.
After all, I'm, I'm a dog.
I have another eight years,
at best.
I'm, I'm willing to give that up
so you can have another 40.
Brian, I...
I-I don't know what to say.
You're savin' my life.
Well, you saved mine.
And, hey, we, we had a lotta
good years together, right?
(voice breaking):
Yeah. We, uh...
we sure did, buddy.
Hello, everyone.
Lois, did you put Stewie to bed?
Yeah, he's asleep.
Good. I'd rather he didn't know
about this till it's over.
He's just a baby.
Now, since the operation is
tomorrow, I thought it might be
a good idea to just kinda close
the book, you know?
So I just wanted to share
my final thoughts
with each one of you.
Meg, you're so beautiful
on the inside,
but it's very important that
you know your limitations.
What do you mean?
Well, I know they say
"Reach for the stars,"
but if we all did that,
there'd be nobody left
here on Earth, right?
I guess.
Ha-ha, there you go.
Chris, I have watched
you grow from a little boy
into the young man
you are today.
I know sometimes
life seems tough,
but you just remember
to reach for the stars.
You really think I can?
I know you can,
slugger!
And, Lois, I only ask this
because of the dire situation
I'm in, but...
can I, can I hump your leg
for 15 uninterrupted seconds?
I suppose so, Brian.
I-I said you could do it
for 15 seconds.
Didn't need it.
No! It can't be!
Where... where am I?
We're at the
playground, Brian.
I kidnapped you.
You and I are going
to spend the rest of our lives
living right here
under the slide.
Stewie, what the hell?
Are you outta your mind?
I most certainly am not!
I know what you're planning
to do, and I won't allow it!
You're not going to kill
yourself for that fat bastard!
Look, I've made up
my mind, all right?
Now untie me.
No, I will not!
How dare you make plans
to abandon me!
Come on, you, you can live
without a dog, Stewie,
but you can't live
without a father.
And besides, h-how exactly
do you think we're supposed
to live here on
the playground?
We'll do fine, Brian!
Everything is right here
where we need it!
The jungle gym is
the grocery store,
the swing set is
the mall,
the seesaw is
the post office,
and the sandbox is
our summer home.
Can you believe it,
Brian?
We, we have
a summer home!
I mean, yes, we'll,
we'll have to rent it out
some years to help pay for...
Oh, no, wait,
no, we won't,
because I'm a famous race car
driver. I forgot!
Stewie, you're not
a race car driver.
And if you don't let
me go right now,
you're gonna lose your dad.
(sniffles) But Brian...
I-I don't wanna lose anybody!
I don't... I don't
wanna lose anybody!
(sobbing)
Oh, my God.
Just stop, stop, just stop it.
But Brian, I love you!
Oh, God,
just wipe your nose, man!
Can I have a hug,
Brian?!
Oh, no, no, God,
no, no, not now, no!
I want a hug!
I love...
No, no. Just wipe...
Oh, God, there's no Kleenex.
I love you, Brian!
I love you so much!
Go... Go roll around
in the sandbox...
in-in-in the summer house!
Go... go to the summer house
and roll around!
Well, here we go.
You know, buddy,
I'm really gonna miss
havin' a dog.
Hey, whaddaya say you be
my dog one last time, huh?
Sure, Peter.
Whatever you want.
Hey, hey, whassat?
Whassat, boy?
Whassat?
Uh, surgical equipment.
Whose is that?
Probably belongs
to the hospital.
Whassat for? Huh?
Whassat for?
Um... cutting me open,
harvesting my organs
and killing me.
You gonna go get it?
You gonna get it, boy?
No, I think, I think
the doctors need it.
Can we, can we
just lay here?
Dr. Hartman,
w-what're you...?
You're not dressed
for surgery.
I sure am.
But I, I don't
understand.
Well, you see, Mrs. Griffin,
I found another donor
for your husband.
You did?! Who?
Me.
What?!
It turns out
I'm a perfect match.
And I'm willing to give up
one of my kidneys.
Oh, my God,
Dr. Hartman,
y-you'd do that
for us?!
Well, the truth is you folks are
my only remaining patients.
I couldn't afford
to lose two of you.
What do you mean,
two of us?
Well, chances are Peter never
would have survived the surgery.
I mean, I mean,
dog kidneys?!
I'm not even sure
dogs have kidneys.
Do dogs have kidneys?
Yes.
Ah, this...
this is the guy.
Oh, my God, Brian...
(all clamoring)
You're gonna live!
Oh, I love you!
I love you!
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
I'm happy to welcome you all
here to our auditorium
for something that's
not a terrible play.
In fact, tonight we're graced
with the presence
of our Commander in Chief.
But first, to introduce him
is a very talented young man,
James Woods' own Chris Griffin.
(applause)
Thank you, Principal Shepherd.
My sister Meg will be helping me
introduce the President,
since we wrote this essay
together.
"What is Hope?" by
Chris and Meg Griffin.
Hope is what gets you
out of bed in the morning
when it's the day of prom
and you haven't been asked.
Hope pushes the
caterpillar
through the cocoon and drives
the salmon upstream.
Your breasts may be small
and your glasses may be thick,
but hope doesn't
hold up a mirror.
CHRIS:
Hope is a horizon we head for,
leaving nothing behind us
but fear.
And though we may never reach
our goals,
it's hope that will save us
from who we once were.
And now...
Ladies and gentlemen...
President Mike Obama!
President Barack Obama!
(soft tremolo chord plays)
♪ You gotta be sincere ♪
(moans)
♪ You gotta feel it here ♪
♪ 'Cause if you feel it here ♪
♪ Well, then you're gonna be ♪
♪ Honestly sincere ♪
(uptempo rhythm plays)
♪ If you're really sincere ♪
♪ If you're really
sincere ♪
♪ If you feel it in here ♪
♪ Then it's gotta be right! ♪
♪ Oh, baby! ♪
(girls squealing)
♪ Oh, honey! ♪
♪ Hug me! ♪
♪ Suffer! ♪
(girls screaming)
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru